Guide to the School of Medicine, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Leon Rosenberg and Robert Berliner, 1953-1987; Accession 1988-A-034
  - Internal Medicine
    - 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - 1975 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Library
    - 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - 1964-1974 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Lung Research Center
    - 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - 1969-1974 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - 1975 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - 1977 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - 1977 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - 1971-1976 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - 1975 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Ad Hoc Committee - Research andDemonstration Center (Box 4, Folder 83 - 84)
  - OB-GYN
    - Nursing - Midwifery
      - 1977 (Box 4, Folder 85)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 86)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 87)
      - 1976 (Box 4, Folder 88 - 89)
    - 1979-1985 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - 1979 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Center for Research in Reproductive Biology, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Opthalmology
    - 1980 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - 1980 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - 1978 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - 1977 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - 1976 (Box 5, Folder 105 - 106)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - Dr. M. Sears, Friededwald Award, 1977 May (Box 5, Folder 108 - 110)
    - 1974 (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - 1975 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Pediatrics
    - 1980-1984 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - 1980 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Pharmacology
    - 1980 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - 1978 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - 1974-1977 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - 1974 (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - 1974-1982 (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - 1982 (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - Pharmacology Proposal, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 127 - 128)
    - Psychopharmacology, 1973-1986 (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - Psychiatry
    - 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 131)
    - 1976 (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 133)
    - 1975-1981 (Box 6, Folder 134)
    - 1975 (Box 6, Folder 135)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 136)
    - 1974 (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - 1973 (Box 6, Folder 138)
    - 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 139)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - 1971 (Box 6, Folder 141)
    - 1973 (Box 6, Folder 142)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 143 - 144)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 145 - 146)
    - 1969 (Box 7, Folder 147 - 148)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 149 - 298)
    - 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 299)
    - 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 300)
  - Radiology (Diagnostic)
    - Fee for Service Billing
      - 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 301)
      - 1979 (Box 7, Folder 302)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 303)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 304)
      - 1974 (Box 7, Folder 305 - 306)
    - 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 307)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 308)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 309)
    - 1975 (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 311)
    - 1974 (Box 7, Folder 312)
  - Student Affairs
    - Curriculum
      - 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 313)
      - 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 314)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 315 - 316)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 317)
      - 1974 (Box 7, Folder 318)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 319)
      - 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 320)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 321 - 322)
    - Financial Affairs
      - 1976 (Box 8, Folder 323 - 324)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 325)
      - 1975 (Box 8, Folder 326 - 327)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 328)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 329)
      - 1974 (Box 8, Folder 330)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 331)
      - S. Fiester, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 332 - 333)
      - S. Fiester, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 334 - 335)
    - Guaranteed Student Loan (GSL)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 336)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 337)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 338)
      - 1979 (Box 8, Folder 339)
      - 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 340)
      - 1977 (Box 8, Folder 341)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 342)
      - 1970-1975 (Box 8, Folder 343)
      - 1970 (Box 8, Folder 344)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 345)
      - 1969 (Box 9, Folder 346)
      - 1969-11 (Box 9, Folder 347)
    - Medical School Scholarships
      - 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 350)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 351 - 352)
    - Track System
      - 1972-1977 (Box 9, Folder 353)
      - 1970 (Box 9, Folder 354 - 355)
  - Surgery
    - 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 359)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 360 - 361)
    - 1980 (Box 9, Folder 362 - 365)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 366 - 367)
    - 1979 (Box 9, Folder 368 - 369)
    - Neuropathology (Box 9, Folder 370)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 371)
    - 1978 (Box 9, Folder 372 - 374)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 375)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 376)
    - 1976 (Box 10, Folder 377 - 380)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 381)
    - 1975 (Box 10, Folder 382 - 383)
    - 1973-1975 (Box 10, Folder 384)
    - 1974 (Box 10, Folder 385)
  - General Administrative records
    - Community Health Care Center Plan (CHCP), 1971-1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Connecticut Medicine, 1971-1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Malpractice Insurance information
      - 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - 1971-1976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - 1976 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - 1977 (Box 11, Folder 9 - 13)
      - 1978 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Parking
      - 1974 (Box 11, Folder 15 - 17)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - 1975 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - YNHMC Inc. - Special Board Meetings
        - 1977 Apr 6 (Box 11, Folder 21)
        - 1977 Mar 29 (Box 11, Folder 22)
        - 1977 Apr 14 (Box 11, Folder 23)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 24)
        - 1978 (Box 11, Folder 25)
        - 1978-1982 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Security and Safety
      - 1971-1976 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - 1976 (Box 12, Folder 28 - 29)
      - 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 30)
      - 1979 (Box 12, Folder 31 - 32)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 33)
      - 1980 (Box 12, Folder 34 - 35)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 36)
      - 1981 (Box 12, Folder 37)
      - 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 38)
      - 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Crank Mail
    - 1968-1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - 1968-1976 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - 1965-1975 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 10 - 12)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - 1978 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - 1978-1980 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - no date (Box 14, Folder 17 - 19)
    - 1981-1983 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - 1979-1983 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - 1983 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - 1986 (Box 14, Folder 23 - 24)
    - 1982-1987 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - 1986 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - no date (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - 1986 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - 1985 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - 1974-1977 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Records, circa 1925-1945; Accession 1994-A-041
  - Animals for Experimental Use, 1932-1933, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Anti-Vivisection Letters: E. Cutler, W.B. Cannon, etc., 1921-1935 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Birth Control, 1931-1934 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Birth Control, 1940- 1942 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Building Program in Surgery, Obstetrics and Gynecology, and Pathology, 1926-19/27 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1932-1951 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Conferences, 1932-1938 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1921-1939 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dedication, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Worksheet- 2nd Semester, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Form Letters, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Housing Committee, 1933 November 24 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Inter-American Relations in the Field of Education Conference on (Washington DC.), 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Medical Aptitude Test, 1936-1944 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Medical Economics, 1931-1936 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Meetings and Minutes, 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mental Hygiene, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous, 1926-1941 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - National Research Council: Subcommittee on Inter-American Medical Literature, 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Nebraska, state of: Questionnaires from School of Medicine, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Patents, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Physical Plant, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Research Funding, 1929-1935 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Rutland Hospital Program, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - University Health, Department of, 1926-1935 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Report titled "Survey of Need of the Yale School of Medicine", 1938-1939; Accession 2003-A-046
  - Report titled "Survey of Need of the Yale School of Medicine", 1938-1939 (Box 1)